PERSONAL STATEMENT

I'm a 27 year old Masters Graduate from Leeds Beckett University, currently living in Manchester. I consider myself a well-organised and reliable person who is hardworking and computer literate, with a flexible and proactive attitude towards work.

During my time at university I have undertaken a variety of challenging and exciting projects. This includes projects solely worked on by myself and projects as part of a team where I have designed and developed web applications to meet the marking criteria.

My university focus was on all aspects of web design and development including web application design patterns and modules covering all aspects of databases. Since graduating university I have worked as a Front-end Web Developer and UX Designer expanding my knowledge of the industry and expanding my skills.

RELEVANT SKILLS

HTML5 & CSS3 (SASS/LESS) Javascript (ES6) & JQuery Gulp / Node.js |avascript Frameworks (React|S) Bootstrap, Material UI, GatsbyJS Git & Jenkins (CI Pipelines) Creating NPM packages Adobe Photoshop,& Adobe XD E-commerce A/B Testing Agile practices / JIRA

Responsive Development Search Engine Optimisation Google Analytics XML & ISON Google Adwords (PPC) Wordpress Development Facebook Advertising OO Development Cypress Test Automation

KEY CAPABILITIES

Constant high standard in preparation and production of documents Friendly and approachable, with a positive attitude.

Time Management - Able to plan, organise and priortise work.

Able to work without supervision.

Willingness to learn.

The ability to work as part of an effective team.

Experience of liaising with managing direcctors, colleagues, peers, teachers and lectures, communicating both verbally and written.

Provided 1st and 2nd line support to business users in a large scale organisation.

Presented project work of a high standard and delivered presentations to a varied audience

RECOGNITIONS & FUNDRAISING

Personal Development Award - 2008

Faculty Award for Outstanding contribution to English throughout the academic year - 2008

Gordon Pearson Award for Creative Writing by Joy Yates, editor of the Hartlepool Mail in recognition of outstanding achievement - 2008 Certificate for Achievement for a one year course in Media Studies - 2012 Miles For Men 5K Chairy Race - £180 Raised for Miles For Men Great North Run Half Marathon Charity Race - £420 Raised for Bloodwise Course Rep For University - Masters Degree

REFERENCES

Lorraine Gillions. Cheshire Datasystems Limited Kings Road Stockport

Email: Lorraine.gillions@cdl.co.uk

Ryan Shaw. FinderMonkey Ltd Oulton Institute Leeds

Email: Rvan@findermonkev.co.uk

EDUCATION

From 2016 to 2017

MSc Information & Technology.

Key Modules: Design Patterns for Web Applications, Data Warehouse Models, Responsive Web Development, Project Management.

Leeds Beckett University.

From 2012 to 2016

BSc Hons Computing (2:1).

Key Modules: Production Project, Advanced Internet Development, Advanced Databases.

Leeds Beckett University

From 2009 to 2012

A Level ICT (B), A Level English Combined (C), AS Level Media Studies (A), AS Level Film Studies (B).

Hartlepool Sixth Form College.

From 2004 to 2009

English Language (A), ICT (A), English Literature (B), Humanities (B),

Mathematics (C), Business Studies (C), Science (C).

High Tunstall College of Science.

WORK EXPERIENCE

From December 2019 to Present

Web Developer

Cheshire Datasystems Limited.

From June 2019 to December 2019

UX Executive.

Boohoo Limited.

From October 2018 to June 2019

Front-End Web Developer.

Cheshire Datasystems Limited.

From October 2017 to October 2018

Iunior Web Developer. FinderMonkey Limited.

From August 2015 to September 2015

Database Administrator Hartlepool Borough Council.

From June 2014 to August 2015

IT Support Specialist / Junior Web Developer.

PCC Airfoils - AETC Limited.

From May 2013 to September 2013

Plasma Cutting Operator. Steel Benders UK Limited.

HOBBIES & INTERESTS















Videogames





Cycling



Badminton



Golf



Tennis